# suleyman cihangir



suleyman.cihangir79@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/suleyman-cihangir



https://suleymancihangir.com

# **Summary**

I've been lucky to have a multidisciplinary education and explore many fields of design and art; having these experiences has enriched my practice as a designer. I'm constantly developing my skills and challenging my own perspectives. Design work is always exciting to me because I think that thoughtful design has the power to change lives for the better, make things work easier and more valuable. Design makes the world more beautiful.

# **Experience**



# Digital Designer | Web Developer | Tattoo Artist

Selbstständig

May 2010 - Present (11 years 2 months +)

Designing and developing custom websites for professionals around the globe.



## Kaufmann im Einzelhandel

Praktiker

Aug 2007 - Jun 2010 (2 years 11 months)

#### **SET VICE STATE OF THE PROPERTY OF THE PROPERT**

**OBI Group Holding** 

Aug 2004 - Aug 2007 (3 years 1 month)



## **Produktionsmitarbeiter**

Randstad

Oct 2003 - Aug 2004 (11 months)

#### ••• Kaufmann im Einzelhandel

**OBI** Group Holding

Jul 2001 - Feb 2003 (1 year 8 months)

## **Education**

# Berufliches Schulzentrum Leonberg

Realschulabschluss, metall

Sep 1996 - Jul 1998



#### Obi Bau- und Heimwerkermarkt

Kaufmann im Einzelhandel, Einzelhandel

Sep 1998 - Jul 2001

## **Licenses & Certifications**

- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- Grundlagen der Programmierung: Basiswissen LinkedIn
- Grundlagen der Programmierung: Objektorientiertes Design LinkedIn
- jn JavaScript: Debugging, Performance-Tools, OOP LinkedIn
- **JavaScript Course** Codecademy
- **TACK** HTML Course Codecademy
- **CSS Course** Codecademy

## **Skills**

Social Media • Web Design • Customer Service • Responsive Web Design • Programming • Object Oriented Design • Software Design • Web Development • Front-end Development • Illustration